Hello friends, welcome once again to
your own DFI channel.
Today we will talk about car infection.
What actually happens if the insurance of our vehicle
expires or there is a gap in it, then
we need a photo of the car to renew the insurance of the vehicle. So,
₹250 is charged from us in the name of photos.
Therefore, today we will do
self-infection. So what happens in self-infection is that firstly,
you will
save two hundred and fifty rupees of charge.
Secondly, whatever issues you face in taking photos, all
your other doubts will be cleared through this video.
You will get the link of Self-infection from the company.
Click on the link and it will open. As soon as it
opens, first of all I will
check my vehicle details, vehicle number etc. OK. In
this way, the photo angles have also been given. In
which ways will we take photos, I
clicked on your first click.
Now, after clicking this first click, we will
take a photo of the front right view of this vehicle.
See how the photos will be.
You just have to check that
you clicked the photo in the vehicle.  A blue colour
line will appear there for
hundred percent, as if hundred
percent photo has been uploaded, take the
photo in this way
[Music] the
entire vehicle is being uploaded,
click the photo
[Music]
then again upload your 100 percent photo in the
same way, go to the back side, the entire
vehicle should be visible till the back left side and there should not be any cutting in your vehicle,
then take the back side
photos in this way,
you have done the photo, its sound will come, engine
compartment under wood, what is this,
click on it,
try to submit it with the number plate,
100 percent uploading will
go to the autometer reading, turn
on the key,
start the vehicle,
then take its photo,
take the photo of Sumit, take the
photo,
ok
[Music]
if there is nothing in front or back then you
can also take the photo of friend friend,
you need it, in
which all the four tyres should be
seen in this way, it is called a lot of space, there is an
industrial photo,
now we will submit it,
whatever digits are required in your RC, the vehicle of which you are taking the photo
[Music] we will
wait a little
[Music]